Jens Du Four – System Engineer

Personal Information

!!! 05/07/1997

Ghent

■ Belgian➡ Rijbewijs B

Bachelor Applied Computer

Sciences

jens.dufour@outlook.com

0477 26 51 18 in JensDuFour



Profile

Microsoft 365 Expert Enterprise Administrator Expert

Microsoft Azure Medior
Windows Server Medior
Windows 10 Medior
Docker Medior

40k+ Container Pulls

Enterprise Linux Junior

Languages

SpeakingUnderstandingWritingDutchMother tongueMother tongueMother tongueEnglishFluentFluentFluentFrenchIntermediateIntermediateIntermediate

References

Yuri Karamian +32 493 34 18 68







Career History

Axxes

08/2019 - Present

Client Danone Period 06/2020 –

Location Brussel, Belgium

Description On-Site Support Analyst

Environment:

As a Support Engineer, I provide internal customers with operational and technical support. This is done through a pro-active approach, provide to enable Danone employees to operate more effectively and efficiently. I analyze Customer problems and give advice on appropriate actions. I combine these day-to-day operations with project work.

I redesigned the entire shared PC concept for the organization in BENL. I guided the migration from Symantec Altiris towards Microsoft Endpoint Manager. Migrating the remaining devices in the Danone part of the organization, this was in tandem with the migration I performed at Alpro.

To conclude, I am also part of the "Ways of Working"-team which aims to modernize how the organization works, in terms of digital meetings and online presence, in these trying times.

Tasks:

- Provide technical support to internal customers.
- Ensure positive relationships that are build and maintained with all involved parties (business, team, suppliers).
- Ensure that knowledge and experience are well documented and shared with colleagues.
- Always maintain asset inventory up to date.
- Roles and responsibilities as described by ITIL processes and the Roles & Responsibilities Matrix (i.e., RACI matrix).
- Constantly educate Business in the value & constraints of IT.

Tools:

4ME Help Center (Ticketing system), Symantec Altiris, PowerShell, Batch, Active Directory, Bomgar Remote Support Tool, SharePoint Migration Tool, Cisco WebEx, Microsoft Endpoint Manager, ITIL

Client Alpro

Period 09/2019 – ...

Location Wevelgem, Belgium **Description** W10 Migration Engineer

Environment:

I worked in the internal IT team on the Windows 10 migration project. I was responsible for upgrading +/- 1000 devices, as part of a two men team. These devices where both situated in offices as well as production environments all over Western Europe (UK, GE, NL, BE and FR). Near the end of the project, I also designed and implemented a solution regarding OneDrive and Home Drive on shared devices. I also provided on-site and remote support concerning this project.

Tasks:

- Install and configure new devices using Symantec Altiris
- Upgrade and configure old devices using Symantec Altiris
- Troubleshooting of hardware/software issues
- Automating RecOps using PowerShell and Batch
- Developing user-friendly interfaces using PowerShell and Electron
- Windows Server management
- Active Directory management
- Designing long-term solutions through the process of a change request

Tools:

4ME Help Center (Ticketing system), Symantec Altiris, PowerShell, Batch, Active Directory, Bomgar Remote Support Tool, SharePoint Migration Tool

Client Axxes

Period 08/2019 – 09/2019

Location Antwerp

Description Internal Training – Infrastructure Kickstart Program

During the first weeks, I got 10 full days of training by senior Axxes consultants. During these training days, I got an intensive introduction to different levels of IT infrastructure.

The following topics were covered during this training:

- Windows Server 2019
- Scripting (PowerShell)
- ITIL-principles (v4)
- Linux
- Virtualization: VMWare
- VEEAM
- Office 365 & Azure
- Networking & Security
- SCCM
- Apple Device Management
- Communication/Soft skills

I acquired the ITIL Foundation V4 certificate during these 5 weeks.

Delaware China (Internship)

02/2019 - 04/2019

Location Harbin, China **Description** Trainee

Environment:

I worked in the internal IT team under the system administrator, providing remote support to their offices in Harbin, Suzhou & Shanghai. After a while I provided similar services to their clients.

- Install and configure Delaware Software Center for end user
- Install and configure SAP GUI for end user
- Trouble shooting of office network issue
- Install and configure LAN Driver for end user
- Install and configure Delaware VPN for end user
- Assist to adapt & configure Zoom meeting room
- Assist to maintain office Virtual Machines
- Install Virtual Machine on request
- Windows server management (internal/customer)

Tools:

Omni tracker (Ticketing system), Microsoft Azure, Microsoft SCOM, Service Trace; Workflow Studio (RPA Solution), SAP on Azure

Projects/Workshops System Administrator

10/2018 - 01/2019

Location Ghent, Belgium

Description Student @ University College Ghent

Environment:

In this assignment, the intention was to set up two complete network domains, Windows Server and RHEL Linux, in one team, interconnected, including all typical services: DNS, web, e-mail, etc. I was one of the team leads and it was up to me to manage and decide who took on which tasks to develop, test and deliver. Most assignments depended on each other which made teamwork a key part of the project. This was achieved through technical documentation of the project.

- Install and configure a Domain Controller with DNS
- Install and configure an Exchange Server
- Install and configure a webserver
- Install and configure a DHCP-server
- Install and configure a fileserver
- Install and configure a SharePoint-server with dependencies (SQL)

Tools:

Ansible, Vagrant, Oracle VirtualBox, VMWare Workstation, VMware ESXi, Dell PowerEdge, PowerShell, Cisco IOS, Git

Education and Extra Curricular

2019 2015	Bachelor's in applied computer sciences – University College Ghent Science and Mathematics – IKSO Denderleeuw
2021	Microsoft 365: Enterprise Administrator Expert
2020	Microsoft Certified Trainer
2020	Microsoft 365: Modern Desktop Administrator Associate
2020	Microsoft 365 Certified: Fundamentals
2020	Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals
2019	ITIL® Foundation Certificate in IT Service Management
2018	Follow-up course first aid (Helper)
2018	Basic course first aid
2015	Group leader @ Scouts Ninove

Knowledge and Experience Summary

Client Linux (Ubuntu/Arch), Microsoft 365, Microsoft Intune,

Microsoft Autopilot, Symantec Altiris, Windows 7, Windows

10

Server Active Directory Domain Services, DNS, Windows Server

2016, Windows Server 2019, Linux (RHEL/Ubuntu)

Network CCNA Routing & Switching

Database Oracle Database, MongoDB, MySQL

Virtualization Hyper-V, Microsoft Azure, Oracle VirtualBox, VMWare ESXi

Application Ansible, Bash, Docker, Git, Visual Studio Code

Hardware Aruba Networks, Dell PowerEdge, HP Enterprise, Ubiquiti

Unifi

Security Symantec Endpoint Protection, Certified Network Security

Specialist, Hacker101

Mobile AirWatch MDM, Microsoft Intune (MDM)

Other WordPress, Search Engine Optimization (SEO), Agile

Methodologies, Cryptocurrencies